Air and naval forces of the United States
美国空军和海军
launched a series of strikes against terrorist facilities...
对恐怖组织设施进行了一系列的打击行动
Pan Am flight 103 crashed into the town of Lockerbie.
泛美航空103号航班坠毁于洛克比镇
He has sanctioned acts of terror in Africa, Europe and the Middle East.
他在非洲 欧洲和中东都制裁过恐怖行动
This will not stand, this aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
针对科威特的侵略是不会长久的
This relentless pursuit of terror.
这种对恐怖主义赤裸裸的追求
We will make no distinction...
我们会一视同仁
The USS Cole was attacked while refueling in the port of Aden.
科尔号驱逐舰在亚丁港加油时遭到袭击
This was an act of terrorism.
这是一次恐怖袭击
It was a despicable and cowardly act.
是卑鄙而软弱的行径
The next samba we're going to swing for you is one of the good old favorites.
我们为您带来的下一首桑巴是一首怀旧金曲
...until something stops him.
直到他被阻止
It was right in front of my eyes,
就在我的眼前
and I never saw it coming.
我完全没有料到会出这种事
That plane crashed into the World Trade Center.
那飞机直冲着世贸大楼撞了过去
Thousands of people running.
上千的民众在逃命
We must and we will remain vigilant at home and abroad.
我们必须也会在国内外保持警惕
You're the smartest and the dumbest fucking person I've ever known.
你是我认识的最聪明 也是最笨的人
I'm not the one who got it wrong. I'm the only one who got it right.
弄错的人可不是我 只有我弄对了
Take 'em.
拿下他们
Take 'em all.
统统拿下
Previously on Homeland...
前情提要
I'm an associate at Bennett, Parr and Hamilton.
我是Bennett Parr&Hamilton的一名律师
One of our partners would like to meet with you. Miss Mathison, Leland Bennett.
- 我们有个合伙人想要见你 - Mathison女士 我是Leland Bennett
What does your client want? To pick your brain from time to time.
- 你的客户想要什么? - 时不时从你那里抠点消息
Put you on retainer as it were.
给你点预付金之类的
No sound.
不许出声
Take it off.
脱掉
Carrie Mathison.
Carrie Mathison
It's time we talk about Nasser Hejazi.
我们来谈谈Nasser Hejazi吧
Whose name you used to embezzle more than $45 million.
你用他的名字侵吞了超过四千五百万美元
You are now an enemy of your own state.
你现在是自己国家的敌人
I got plans for you. What plans?
- 我给你定了些计划 - 什么计划?
I'm gonna play you back into Iran. From now on you work for us.
我要把你送回伊朗 从现在开始你为我们工作
For me.
为我工作
I've recruited a high-level Iranian asset. Majid Javadi.
我招募了一名伊朗高层情报员 Majid Javadi
The man who financed the bombing of the CIA?
那个为CIA爆炸案出资的人?
We talked about this.
我们谈过了
The need to wean you of your cold war bullshit.
我们得让你忘记冷战之类的废话
This is a once in a lifetime operation that can transform everything.
这是一次百年难遇的好机会 这样可以改变一切
The entire Middle East. You sound like you're fucking high.
- 改变整个中东 - 你他妈喝高了吧
I need to know something before you leave. I need to know...
在你走之前 我要问你一个问题 告诉我...
who's responsible for the bomb?
炸弹是谁制造的?
You know what he asked me? Who moved the bomb?
你知道他问了我什么? 谁移动了炸弹
If it was Brody. Now, why would he ask me that?
是不是真的是Brody 他为什么要问我这个问题?
That implies that there's a difference of opinion on that subject.
也就是说有人对此持不同意见
You should know that the man who built the bomb and moved the SUV,
你应该知道制造炸弹并且移动SUV的人
he didn't die in the explosion like they say.
他没有像外界所传的那样死在爆炸中
As far as I know, he's still in this country. Where?
- 据我所知 他还在美国 - 哪里?
I don't know. Who does?
- 我不知道 - 谁知道?
The man that brought us together. Your lawyer? Bennett?
- 让我们见面的人 - 你的律师 Bennett?
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 国土 第三季第8集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 国土 第三季第8集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：RoyJames
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：菱子 校对：Onlyonly9喝大酒来 时间轴：RoyJames
Fuck!
操!
What happened to you?
你这是怎么了?
I started to get worried. I'm out of practice.
- 我开始着急了 - 我手生了
Well...
嗯...
this looks delicious, Saul.
看起来很好吃 Saul
Thank you.
谢谢
Can I pour you a cup of tea? Please.
- 要我给你倒杯茶吗? - 好的
Where did you get these from?
你从哪里弄到这些的?
Aren't these the mugs we brought back from the Philippines?
这不是我们从菲律宾买回来的杯子么?
The very last pair.
就剩这一对了
When this is all over,
当这一切结束以后
I'd like to go back to that island on the Sulu Sea.
我想回Sulu Sea上的那个岛
You know, you don't have to promise anything.
你不需要给我做任何承诺
Really. I understand.
真的 我理解
No, I don't see why not. We might actually have fun.
不 这样没什么不好的 说不定我们会玩得很开心呢
Well, the evidence does seem to indicate that that is possible
嗯 毕竟证据的确显示
after all.
有这种可能性
Is there any chance
有没有可能
that you could stay home today?
你今天可以呆在家里?
There's nothing I'd rather do.
我没其他想干的事
But?
但是?
I got a meeting with Mike Higgins this morning at the White House.
我今晚要去白宫和Mike Higgins会面
- When? - 9:30.
- 什么时候? - 9点半
Well, that gives us an hour and a half...
嗯 那我们还有一个半小时...
by my count.
据我看来
Yes, it does.
是啊 的确
Okay, here's something.
好吧 找到一个
Dr. Maximillian Aziz, Jordanian,
Maximillian Aziz博士 约旦人
was actually in the auditorium the time the bomb went off.
爆炸的时候他正在礼堂里
Ops or Intelligence? Intelligence- Office of Transnational Issues.
- 行动人员还是情报人员? - 情报人员 国际性问题办公室的
And what's his connection to Leland Bennett?
他和Leland Bennett有什么关联?
He wrote a lengthy analysis of the firm's hip-pocket clients.
他针对事务所的非正式客户写过一篇冗长的分析
Iran, Syria, Azerbaijan. This was two years ago.
伊朗 叙利亚 阿塞拜疆 是两年前的事
It hardly fits the profile.
跟侧写几乎对不上啊
Any munitions training? Experience with explosives?
有没有接受过武器训练? 有没有接触过爆炸物?
Uh... no.
呃 没有
All right, add him to the list anyway. Yeah, which begs the question-
- 好吧 还是把他先放进名单里吧 - 嗯 这就引起个问题
are we even sure that the guy who made the bomb moved Brody's car?
我们到底确不确定是制造炸弹的人 动了Brody的车?
- Depends. - On what?
- 那得看 - 看什么?
On whether or not you believe Javadi.
看你相不相信Javadi
- Which you do. - Which I do.
- 你是相信的 - 我是相信的
But it takes more than an opinion to put it in front of Saul.
但是要和Saul提的话 光靠说是不够的
Right.
是的
You know, I can't help but feel we're spinning our wheels here.
你知道么 我有一种很强烈的 我们在碰运气的感觉
The FBI have been through these files a hundred times.
FBI已经把这些档案查过几百次了
Anybody that was at Langley that day has been turned inside-out and upside-down.
任何那一天在兰利的人 祖宗八百代都被查遍了
Yeah, well, someone who was at Langley that day did the bombing.
是啊 嗯 那天在兰利的某人引爆了炸弹
I still can't believe all these people are gone.
我还是不能相信这些人就这么没了
Yeah.
是啊
Where's Fara anyway? She was supposed to be here over an hour ago.
Fara到底上哪儿去了? 她一个小时以前就应该来了
- Come on in, Saul. - Hey, Mike.
- 请进 Saul - 你好 Mike
Good to see you.
很高兴见到你
Senator?
参议员先生?
Yeah.
嗯
The Senator's made some serious allegations.
参议员对你做出了一些很严肃的指控
Which are?
都有哪些?
That you had Majid Javadi in a safe house,
说你把Majid Javadi关在美国境内的
on American soil and let him go.
一间安全屋 然后又放他走了
Do you contest that?
你有什么要反驳的吗?
Yes and no. What's the yes?
- 有 也没有? - 你要说什么
I'm not aware of any standing order to arrest Colonel Javadi.
我并没有收到任何逮捕Javadi上校的命令
- Did you have him in custody or not? - I did.
- 你到底有没有拘禁他? - 我拘禁了
Aw, Jesus fucking Christ, Saul. We didn't just "Let him go," Mike.
- 我操你妈 Saul - 我们没有就这么"放他走" Mike
We debriefed him. Turned him.
我们询问了他 让他转投我们
Sent him back to Iran. You turned him?
- 然后送他回伊朗 - 你让他转投我们了?
He's ours. With no guarantee that he'll actually cooperate.
- 他是我们的人了 - 你不能保证他就会乖乖听话
- He will. - How do you know?
- 他会的 - 你怎么知道?
Because I know the man. Because he knows the game.
因为我了解那人 因为他了解游戏规则
That is total speculation. He's right.
- 那完全就是猜测 - 他说得对
We haven't had a whole lot of success - in that department lately. - Well, we have now.
- 我们最近在这一点上毫无建树 - 现在有了
Javadi's the highest placed CIA asset in the history of the Agency.
Javadi是中情局有史以来招募的最高级资产
He ordered and financed the attack on Langley.
他下令并资助了兰利爆炸案
All the better if he did. He's above suspicion.
如果真是这样就更好了 他不会受到怀疑
A high-profile arrest would've sent a clear message to the Mullahs.
高调逮捕会给伊斯兰政要一个更明确的信息
Back the fuck down.
给我他妈的退回去
Instead we have a live source, keeping us current on Iran's pursuit of a nuclear weapon,
但现在我们有了一个实时消息源 我们可以随时知道伊朗核武器的进展
on Hezbollah operations all over the globe.
以及全球黎巴嫩真主党的动向
How come I never saw a finding on this? We were responding to events on the ground.
- 为什么我没有看到结果报告? - 我们要对事件进行当场反应
The call had to be made in real time.
决定都是当时做出的
That is horseshit, and he knows it.
这他妈是胡说 他自己知道
Mike, I think it's time you excuse the Senator.
Mike 我觉得你该送议员先生走了
What are you talking about?
你什么意思?
I called this meeting to brief the Chief of Staff on the second phase of the mission.
我安排这次会面是想和办公厅主任 报告行动的第二阶段
- So, go ahead. - I can't.
- 那说啊 - 不行
- Not with you present. - Why not?
- 你在我就不能说 - 为什么不行?
Because your security clearance is one level below operational.
因为你的安全级别比操作低一级
You see what I'm dealing with?
你看到了吧?
The man is out of hand and out of control.
这个人完全就失控了 完全没法收拾
And in this case, he's correct. I'm sorry, Senator.
就眼下的情况 他是对的 抱歉 议员先生
Mike, in nine days, I'm the next DCI.
Mike 9天以后我就是新的中情局局长
And in nine days, Saul will brief you on whatever you need to know.
Saul可以在9天以后告诉你 一切你想知道的
- But not until then. - Mike...
- 但是现在不行 - Mike...
Senator.
议员先生
- Mike? - Senator, please.
- Mike? - 议员先生 请吧
Goddamn it, Saul.
你个混蛋 Saul
I spent the last month and a half arranging a marriage between you two.
我花了一个半月的时间 想要让你们联手协作
I'm out, I know that.
我出局了 我知道
You are now. You didn't need to be.
你现在的确出局了 没必要这样的
Javadi was worth it.
Javadi值得我这样做
All right, tell me about this phase two.
好了 和我说第二阶段吧
Regime change?
政权交替?
Eventually. We're setting the stage.
最终目的 我们正在准备时机
How?
怎样?
First we move Javadi up the chain of command into a senior military position.
首先 我们让Javadi晋升到一个 指挥系统中的高级军官位置上去
How?! Keep reading.
- 怎样啊?! - 读下去
Sorry I'm late.
抱歉我迟到了
Traffic.
堵车
I ordered you a macchiato, but it's probably cold by now.
我给你点了一杯牛奶咖啡 但是现在大概已经冷了
Thank you.
谢谢
It's fine.
很好喝
So I got your text. Everything okay?
我收到你的短信了 没事吧?
Yes.
嗯
No.
不
It's... Saul.
是...Saul
What about him?
他怎么了?
We've made a decision. Well, I-I've made a decision.
我们做了一个决定 嗯 我做了一个决定
To give the marriage another chance.
我想再给我们的婚姻一次机会
I...
我...
You have to know, it's not easy for me.
你得知道 我做这决定不容易
And when, uh, did you decide all this?
你是什么时候决定的?
Last night.
昨晚
Forgive me, but didn't we just spend yesterday in a suite
抱歉 但是我们昨天不是在Ritz Carlton的
at the Ritz Carlton?
套间里度过的吗?
What's changed?
出什么事了?
I- I just told you.
我...我和你说过了
What, suddenly Saul and you have decided to reconcile?
怎么 突然间Saul和你就决定和好了?
It's not suddenly.
不是突然间
We've been talking about it for the last two months. You know that.
我们就这事已经说了两个月了 你知道的
Well, I was under the impression that you had given up on that.
你给我的感觉是你已经放弃了
That you both had. Well, I don't know, maybe we had.
- 你们都放弃了 - 嗯 我不知道 或许我们是放弃过
Then there's something you're not telling me.
那就是你有事瞒着我
- We've been married 35 years. - I love you.
- 我们结婚已经35年了 - 我爱你
Don't say that. I love making love to you.
- 别这么说 - 我喜欢和你上床
- I have to go. - Mira...
- 我得走了 - Mira...
Good-bye.
再见
He signed off? Well, let's put it this way-
- 他批了? - 嗯 这么说吧
he sees the merits of the operation. So he's taking it to the President?
- 他觉得这行动有好处 - 所以他会去给总统看?
- Yes. - Merits?
- 是的 - 好处?
Saul, it's fucking genius. If we can pull it off.
- Saul 这太他妈天才了 - 如果我们能够成功的话
- When are you leaving? - Tomorrow morning.
- 你什么时候走? - 明早
Does Carrie know you're going? She can't even suspect it.
- Carrie知道你去吗? - 她想都想不到的
Heard you were looking for me.
听说你们在找我
Yeah, we were just going over the transcript of your debrief with Javadi
是啊 我们正在看你给Javadi汇报情况的文本
to see if it supported what he told Carrie - on the tarmac yesterday. - Which was?
- 看看他说的和他昨天在机场告诉Carrie的是否相符 - 是什么?
That the man who moved the SUV is still in the United States,
移动SUV的人还在美国
and he's somehow connected to Leland Bennett's law firm.
他和Leland Bennett的律师事务所有某种联系
- Connected how? - It's unclear.
- 什么联系? - 还不清楚
We were hoping you could shed some light. Javadi didn't mention the Bennett connection.
- 我们还希望你能给我们指点一下呢 - Javadi没有提到Bennett的联系
Well, what about Brody? Did he mention Brody?
那么Brody呢? 他有没有提到Brody?
In what context?
你指什么?
In the context of being the bomber.
是说他有没有可能是炸弹犯
Not in so many words, he didn't. Well, what did he say?
- 没说多少 他没说 - 那他说了什么?
He said as far as he knows, Brody didn't move the car.
他说据他所知 车子不是Brody动的
As far as he knows?
据他所知?
That's not what he told me.
他可不是这么和我说的
- Okay. - He told me definitively it wasn't Brody.
- 好吧 - 他很肯定地告诉我说不是Brody
What's your point? Why would he tell us two different stories?
- 你想说什么? - 为什么他要给我们两人不同的说法?
Is that a question or an accusation?
你是提问还是质问啊?
Well, I guess I'd like a straight answer.
我想要直截了当的答案
And if Javadi even intimated that Brody didn't move the car, why not press him on who did?
如果Javadi都暗示过车子不是Brody动的 为什么你不逼他说出是谁?
Well, you're angry because I didn't share a conversation with you about Brody.
你生气是因为我没告诉你 我们关于Brody的谈话
An inconclusive one.
一段模棱两可的谈话
No, I'm angry because you seem entirely indifferent to catching the actual bomber.
不 我生气是因为你看上去完全 不像是想要抓住真凶
Speak for yourself. I'm all for it. Well, I'm glad to hear it.
- 别胡说 我一心想抓住他 - 啊 很高兴听到你这么说
So... you two... actually have a plan?
所以...你们两个... 有没有计划啊?
Yeah. Yeah, we want to flush this guy out into the open.
有 有 我们想要把这人赶出来
Mm-hmm. How?
嗯 怎样?
You know Leland Bennett personally, right?
你认识Leland Bennett本人 对吧?
We've golfed Congressional a few times together.
一起在国会打过几次高尔夫
And we serve on the board of the Northam Foundation.
而且我们都是Northam基金会的懂事
How comfortable would you be making an approach?
如果要你去接近他你愿意吗?
Comfortable enough.
没什么不愿意的
Oh, back already? Yeah, I'm not feeling well.
- 哦 已经回来了? - 是啊 我不舒服
You can go. I'll look after him today.
你可以走了 今天我来照顾他
You sure? Yeah. How is he?
- 你确定? - 是的 他怎样啊?
Oh, sitting up. Progress.
- 哦 坐起来了 - 有进展
Yeah, slowly but surely.
是啊 很慢 但的确有进展
I'll see you tomorrow.
明天见
Feel better. Thanks.
- 赶快好起来 - 谢谢
Baba Joon.
亲爱的老爸
I'm staying home today.
今天我在家
Do I need a reason?
我需要理由吗?
I'm not going to lose my job.
我不会丢掉工作的
Because I'm sure.
因为我确定
Speak English.
说英语
English.
英语
I did not come to America to live in the street like a dirty Arab.
我来美国可不是为了像个 肮脏的阿拉伯人一样露宿街头
Baba... listen to me.
爸爸 听我说
Nothing like that is going to happen. No one's going to throw us out of our home.
那是不可能的 没有人会把我们赶出我们家
Don't worry.
别担心
My job's safe.
我不会丢工作的
At the bank?
银行的工作?
Yes.
是的
At the investment bank.
投资银行的工作
If you work at the bank,
如果你在银行工作
why are we not rich?
那我们为什么还没钱?
Richter. That's a German surname. My parents were born in Hamburg.
- Richter 这是德国姓啊 - 我父母是在汉堡出生的
Do you speak it? Ja nat眉rlich.
- 会说德语吗? - 是的 当然
That's useful.
这很有用
We represent three private banking houses in Berlin.
我们在柏林有客户是三家私人银行
Would you, uh, excuse me for just a moment?
能不能 呃 容我失陪一下?
Of course.
当然
You're early.
你来早了
I'm in the middle of interviewing a new associate. It won't take long.
- 我还在面试新秘书呢 - 不会花很久的
We missed you at the foundation meeting last week.
上周基金会会议你没有去啊
Couldn't get there. Work.
没法去 公务
You gotta make time for us.
你得补偿给我们
It's not enough that I've raised over a million dollars this quarter?
我这个季度给你们拉了 一百多万的捐款还不够吗?
You know me. Never satisfied.
你了解我的 多多益善
But... that's not what this is about.
但是...我来不是为了这事
- No? - No.
- 不是? - 不是
Sounds ominous.
我有不详的预感
I do terror now, by the way.
顺便说一句 我现在管反恐
I'm not sure you knew that. I don't think I did.
- 我觉得你应该不知道吧 - 我好像真不知道
Your firm's name has come up lately. More than once.
你事务所的名字最近出现了 不止一次
- In what light? - That I can't tell you.
- 什么原因? - 这我不能和你说
Then why tell me at all?
那为什么还要告诉我?
Because tomorrow morning at exactly 10:00, I walk into a high level,
因为明天早上10点整 我会参与一个高层的
top secret meeting at which you are the agenda.
绝密的会议 就是讨论你们事务所的
What do you want?
你想要什么?
Cooperate with us. Come clean.
和我们合作 都说出来
Get out in front of what's sure to turn into a...
现在赶紧脱身 别等我们对你进行...
a bruising investigation.
会让你伤元气的调查
You know what?
这么跟你说吧
20 years ago, I might've fallen for that weak shit.
20年前 我说不定还会上你的狗当
But today...
但是现在...
come after me if you want. I've got nothing to hide.
想来找茬尽管来 我光明磊落
Text a red wheel barrow.
(- 那么多的东西都依靠... - 一辆红色的手推车)
Who's the candle for?
给谁点的蜡烛?
All the departed.
所有的逝者
You Orthodox?
你是正教的吗?
Old boyfriend.
以前的男友是
I hear the weddings go on forever.
我听说婚礼没完没了的
Longer than the marriages, so goes the joke.
有个笑话说比婚姻本身还要长
Mr. Bennett needs you to look into something for him.
Bennett先生需要你去查样东西
My arrangement's with Majid Javadi,
我是被安排给Majid Javadi的
not Leland Bennett. Correct.
- 不是Leland Bennett - 的确
But what Mr. Bennett heard today might reverberate onto you.
但是Bennett先生今天听说的事 有可能会返回到你身上
Onto me? Do I need to remind you-
- 我身上? - 需不需要我提醒你
you're a recruited agent of a foreign government?
你是外国政府的雇佣情报员?
I met with Javadi. Once.
我见过Javadi 就一次
I agreed to consult with him. I'm nobody's agent.
我同意给他咨询 我不是谁的情报员
I doubt the CIA would appreciate the distinction. What the hell do you know about it?
- 我觉得CIA应该不会去区分吧 - 你他妈又知道什么?
I know the law firm appears to be the target of an inquiry of some kind.
我知道律师事务所会受到某种审查
Well, not one that I'm aware of.
嗯 这我不知道
The warning was delivered personally,
警告是有人亲自告知的
outside of official channels.
通过非官方渠道
By somebody who works at the Agency?
是某个局里的人?
A longtime acquaintance of Mr. Bennett, yes.
Bennett先生的一位旧识 是的
So what do you want from me?
你要我干什么?
Confirm the report.
确认情报
Mr. Bennett needs to know what part of the business is under investigation
Bennett先生需要知道事务所的 哪一块会受到调查
and what he can do to protect himself.
以及他该如何保护自己
That's not going to be easy. Not without setting off alarm bells.
这不会容易的 这样会打草惊蛇的
You'll figure something out. I'll figure something out?
- 你去想办法 - 我去想办法?
And obviously there's a clock on this. Obviously.
- 还有显然这事是有时间期限的 - 显然
Hello? It's on.
- 喂? - 开始了
Tell me. I just met with Franklin.
- 说说看 - 我刚刚和Franklin见面了
They're panicking over there. Well, let them.
- 他们惊慌了 - 让他们慌去
Wait 24 hours...
等24小时...
then hit them with the news we know who the bomber is.
然后告诉他们我们知道炸弹犯是谁了
Will do.
好的
Uh, Saul?
呃 Saul?
Yeah?
在
I need some personal time between then and now.
到那时为止我需要独处一下
You got it.
好的
- Thanks. - You all right?
- 谢谢 - 你没事吧?
Yeah.
嗯
I should've shared that intel about Brody with you sooner.
我应该早一些告诉你关于Brody的情报的
I'm sorry, I wasn't thinking. You've been to hell and back.
抱歉 我没想仔细 你是去了一趟鬼门关
I know how important this is to you.
我知道这消息对你来说有多重要
I owe you. We all do.
我欠你 我们都是
Yeah, well, as long as we get the real bomber...
嗯 只要我们抓住真凶...
We will.
我们会的
Carrie?
Carrie?
Yeah. How'd you know? Tone of your voice.
- 是的 你怎么知道的? - 你说话的口气
You don't talk to anyone else like that.
对别人你不会用那种语气
Huh, I wasn't aware. You ready to eat?
- 啊 我没注意过 - 准备好吃饭了吗?
Should I open a bottle of wine? That's a great idea.
- 要不要开一瓶酒? - 这主意不错
Listen... I got to go away for a few days.
听着... 我得离开两天
You do?
是吗?
- Yeah. - When?
- 是的 - 什么时候?
Tomorrow.
明天
Saul... I know.
- Saul... - 我知道
The timing's not great.
时机不太好
But you said only a couple of days?
但是你说就两天?
Yeah. A week, at the most.
是啊 最多一周
A week?
一周?
I wouldn't be going...
如果不是绝对必要...
if I didn't absolutely have to.
我不会这么做的
You know what, I could go with you.
你知道么 我可以和你一起去
- Wouldn't that be great? - Why not?
- 那样不太好吧 - 为什么不好?
It's not that kind of trip.
不是那种旅行
I wish it were.
我真希望是
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- 干杯
To us.
敬我们
You've been nauseous? Yeah.
- 你老是想吐? - 是的
Usually that goes away by now.
通常现在已经不会了
So I've heard.
我也是这么听说的
I'm getting a real clear image here.
我这里的成像很清晰
You want to know if it's a boy or a girl?
你想知道是男孩还是女孩吗?
No.
不
Sorry this is so last-minute. No, no, it's great to see you.
- 抱歉临时来找你 - 不 不 能见到你真好
This is quite a surprise.
真是意外之喜啊
I saw Maggie at the hospital last week, she didn't say a thing.
我上周在医院见过Maggie 她什么也没说
She doesn't know.
她不知道
Does that have anything to do with why you're coming in for your first prenatal exam
你怀孕13个星期才来做检查
13 weeks in?
和这有关系吗?
I didn't exactly plan this.
这不是计划之中的
But you've known for some time.
但是你已经知道一阵了
What about medications? What are you currently taking?
药呢? 最近你在吃什么药?
Uh, at the moment, nothing. I see.
- 呃 目前没有 - 哦
I was on 1,800 milligrams of lithium for about a month there.
我吃了大约一个月1800毫升的锂盐
Things were a little out of control.
生活有些失控
And, uh, before that, there was a lot of drinking.
还有 呃 在那之前 我喝了很多酒
A... lot.
很...多
After you knew?
在你知道以后?
I haven't been painting a nursery, just put it that way.
这么说吧 我没有准备婴儿房
Are you telling me you wish to terminate?
你是说你不希望要这个孩子?
I just want to know what the tests say. If things are okay.
我只想知道化验结果是什么 是不是一切安好
Well...
嗯...
you're iron deficient.
你缺铁
We can fix that. But your blood pressure's very high.
这很容易解决 但是你血压很高
I've been... really stressed at work.
我最近...工作上的压力很大
Well, you really should be taking it easy.
嗯 你真的应该放松点
Yeah, I'll try.
嗯 我试试吧
Carrie, we can manage this. Keep you and the baby healthy.
Carrie 我们可以做到的 让你和宝宝都健健康康的
It's not magic, it's a process.
那不是魔法 那是努力
You want to leave it to chance, that's up to you.
你想要靠运气 那就只能随你了
Otherwise you need to modify your behavior.
不然你就得改变一下你的行为
Not in a week or two, or when it's convenient.
不是一两周以后 不是趁你方便的时候
Now.
就现在
What I'm doing, it has to do with the father. I need to make some things right.
我现在做的事和孩子的父亲有关 我需要把一些事情处理好
It matters to a lot of people.
这对很多人来说都很重要
But this is different, Carrie. You're not on your own anymore.
但是这不一样啊 Carrie 这不仅仅关系到你一个人啊
Fara? Sherazi?
Fara Sherazi?
And you are? Mitchell Clausen.
- 你是? - Mitchell Clausen
From the IG's Office.
我是IG办公室的
IG? Inspector General.
- IG? - 总检察长
May I come in?
我能进去吗?
This way.
这边
May I offer you something? I'm good. Um...
- 您想喝点什么? - 不用了 嗯...
you called in sick two days in a row.
你连续两天请了病假
Is something the matter? Migraines.
- 有什么不对吗? - 偏头痛
Yet you drove into work yesterday. Yes.
- 但是你昨天开车上班了 - 是的
Where you sat in the parking lot for over half an hour before deciding to leave again.
你在停车场坐了半个多小时 然后又决定离开
I was hoping the headache would go away.
我本来希望头痛可以停止的
Is that why you then paid a visit to 1426 Longhill Road,
你是不是就是因为这个 所以才去了Longhill路1462号
where the recent double murder happened?
就是双重谋杀案的发生地?
The Bethesda PD took down your license number.
Bethesda警方拍到了你的车牌号
The Agency had to call in a lot of favors to close that investigation.
中情局找了很多人才终止调查
Your going over there jeopardized all that.
你去那里让我们的努力全白费了
I wanted to see where it happened.
我想看看出事的地方
Why?
为什么?
It upset me. I... I was upset by it.
那事让我很难过 我...我觉得很难过
Director Berenson has shown an unusual degree of confidence in you, Ms. Sherazi...
Berenson局长对你异乎寻常的信任 Sherazi女士
Entrusted you with matters of national importance.
将国家安全的重任委任与你
I'm aware of that.
我知道这一点
But your current state of mind makes your loyalty to him
但是你目前的思想状态使得我们不得不三思
and to the Agency a very live issue.
你对他和中情局的忠诚度
Tell the Director not to worry.
请告诉局长不要担心
I'm fine. You can tell him yourself.
- 我没事 - 你自己去和他说吧
When you come into work tomorrow.
明天上班的时候去
Yes.
是的
Director Berenson?
Berenson局长?
Who is this Director Berenson?
这个什么Berenson局长是谁?
My boss.
我的老板
But he's no banker, is he?
但是他不是开银行的 对不对?
No.
对
You went ahead, didn't you?
你还是做了 对不对?
In spite of everything I said?
我跟你说的话你当耳边风吗?
Baba, an attack happened. So what?
- 爸爸 有人被攻击了 - 所以呢?
It's none of your business.
这不关你的事啊
They needed Farsi speakers with experience in international finance.
他们需要会说波斯语 又有国际金融工作经验的人
I had to help.
我得去帮忙啊
And when the secret police find out who you work for, what then?
如果秘密警察发现了以后怎么办?
We have family still in Tehran!
我们在德黑兰还有家人呢!
Your uncle, his wife and children.
你的叔叔还有他的妻儿
They will be added to the list of those to be hanged,
他们会被加入黑名单 被吊死
or shot!
被打死!
I'm an American.
我是美国人
Target is still unknown, but presumed to be the man
目标还不清楚 但是应该是那个
who put the bomb in position in front of the HQ auditorium.
将炸弹车开到总部礼堂前面的人
This is Paul Franklin, our stalking horse. Carrie?
这是Paul Franklin 我们的试探 Carrie?
Later this afternoon, I'll promote misinformation
今天下午较晚的时候 我会把错误情报
to Mr. Franklin in the hopes that he'll lead us to the bomber.
告诉Franklin先生 希望他可以带我们找到炸弹犯
Our assumption is that after the meeting, he'll reach out for instructions.
我们的假设是在会面结束后 他会打电话向上级咨询
To this man. Leland Bennett, one of the senior partners at the firm.
是这个人 Leland Bennett 事务所的资深合伙人之一
Which is why operation, from this moment forward,
所以这次行动 从现在开始
requires a full complement of audio and visual surveillance on both subjects.
需要对这两个人进行全面的声像监控
I don't have to tell you what catching this guy would mean.
不需要我告诉你们 抓到这个人的意义了吧
In other words, stay small, stay cool, stay out of sight.
也就是说 做小伏低 不要轻举妄动 不要随意露面
Okay, everybody. Game time.
好了 各位 行动开始
You were right. Tell me.
- 你说对了 - 告诉我
They've connected your firm to the guy who detonated the bomb at Langley.
他们把你的事务所和在兰利 引爆炸弹的人联系到一起了
That's not possible. I'm telling you what I found out.
- 那不可能 - 我只是跟你说我的发现
All right. Okay.
好吧 好
They're also under the impression that he's still here in the United States.
他们还有感觉说这个人现在还在美国
Is that true?
是不是这样?
Answer the question, or so help me, I'll get up and you'll never see me again.
回答我的问题 不然的话我就走人 你这辈子也别想再见到我
Take it easy, Carrie. Take a breath. No, don't patronize me.
- 放松点 Carrie 深呼吸 - 别一副主人的样子
Okay. It's true, he's here.
好吧 没错 他是在这里
He's here where?
这里是哪里?
I'm assuming that means they haven't located him yet.
这就说明他们还没有找到他的确切位置
No, they haven't. Then exactly what do they have?
- 不 还没有 - 那他们到底发现了什么?
A warrant pending before a FISA judge, naming Leland Bennett a co-conspirator.
已经向外国情报监视法案的法官申请搜捕令 指控Leland Bennett为共犯
How soon before the warrant's active? A few days, at least.
- 搜捕令什么时候生效? - 至少也得等几天吧
They won't find anything. Bennett's clean. He works through a cutout.
他们什么也不会找到的 Bennett是干净的 他已经想到脱身的方法了
You.
你
Just lay low and let me handle this.
低调点 让我来处理吧
You're the one who's been handling this, so excuse me if your assurance isn't very assuring.
你本来就是处理这事的人 所以你让我安心我可一点不觉得安心
They have a line on our friend. How'd they get onto him?
- 他们有我们朋友的线索了 - 他们怎么找到他的?
- No idea. - Well, find out.
- 不知道 - 去找出来
It's a little late for that, don't you think? You sure it wasn't your mistake?
- 现在做这个是不是有点晚了? - 你确定不是你犯了错误?
You sure it wasn't yours?
你确定不是你犯了错?
We were asked to provide material support to an American citizen with ties to the Regime.
我们被要求提供物资支持给一个 和伊朗政权有关联的美国公民
There was no mention of his involvement in the bombing.
并没有提到他参与了爆炸案
There was later. Yes, there was.
- 后来有了 - 是啊 有
Well, we should've dealt with it then.
我们那时就应该处理掉的
Maybe.
或许吧
Do they know his name? No.
- 他们知道他的名字吗? - 不知道
Then we're still okay. Do you want him out of the country?
- 那我们就不会有事 - 你想要送他出国吗?
Yes.
是的
Preferably with a new identity.
最好是用新身份
How much do I tell him? I don't care.
- 我要告诉他多少? - 我不在乎
Just get him out.
赶紧把他弄走
Franklin's sending a text. Talk to me.
- Franklin发短信了 - 告诉我是什么
It's an address and time.
是地址和时间
Fairview Motel in Lynchburg, 0130.
Lynchburg的Fairview汽车旅馆 0130
Can we trace who he's sending it to? No, there must be an anonymizer on the device.
- 能不能追踪到是发给谁的? - 不能 手机上一定是加了匿名器
Don't worry, Carrie.
别担心 Carrie
As long as we stick on Franklin, you'll get your bomber.
只要我们盯紧了Franklin 就会抓到炸弹犯的
He's right.
他说得对
We'll send a tactical team to the motel.
我们会派一个战略小队去汽车旅馆
They'll arrest the target as soon as Franklin clears scene.
一旦Franklin离开现场 他们就会逮捕目标
DC Department of Transportation is warning drivers to prepare for delays
华府运输部提醒各位司机 在周四到周六
due to street closures downtown Thursday through Saturday.
某些路段会关闭 有可能引起堵塞
Officials say southbound 14th Street Northwest
官方说南向的西北14街
will be closed between G Street and Pennsylvania.
在G街和宾夕法尼亚街路段会关闭
Here's something.
有动静了
It could be him.
有可能是他
Yeah, it is him. I've got a visual.
对 就是他 我看清楚了
Copy that.
收到
What's he doing? Just sitting there at the moment.
- 他在干吗? - 眼下就只是坐着
Bravo, do you have eyes on?
Bravo 你们看得到吗?
I'm looking down on the roof of his car.
我正在看着他的车顶
No one moves until Franklin leaves site.
在Franklin离开现场之前都不要动
Copy that.
收到
He's calling someone. We got it.
- 他在打电话 - 我们接收到了
Are you here? Outside.
- 你来了吗? - 在外面
Flash your lights.
闪一下车灯
What room are you in? First tell me what's happening.
- 你在哪个房间? - 先告诉我出了什么事
You may have been compromised.
你好像已经暴露了
How the hell did that happen? It happened.
- 到底他妈的出了什么事? - 事情已经出了
What difference does it make how? Because I'm the one whose life is fucked.
- 现在还有区别吗? - 因为生活被人毁了的人是我
If I hadn't gotten to you first, you'd spend the rest of your life living in a cage.
如果不是我先找到你 你下半辈子就蹲监狱去吧
Try on some gratitude. You want your exfil package or not?
所以感谢下我们吧 你到底要不要你的撤出包啊?
2-2-0. Be right up.
- 220 - 马上上去
Shit. He's got a weapon.
该死 他有武器
What?
什么?
Now he's silencing it. Jesus, you seeing this?
现在他在上消声器 天啊 你们看到没有?
He's got a gun! Bravo, can you confirm?
- 他有枪! - B队 能否确认?
Negative. My view is obscured.
不能 我这个角度看不到
He's not exfiltrating the bomber, he's taking him out. You don't know that, Carrie.
- 他不是想要帮罪犯偷渡出去 他是要杀了他 - 你不能下定论 Carrie
Why else would he have a silencer?
那他为什么要装消音器?
She's right, Scott. I make the weapon.
她说得对 Scott 我看到武器了
I'm telling you Franklin's gonna kill that guy.
我告诉你 Franklin会杀了那人
Listen to me. We just heard Bennett telling Franklin to get the guy out of the country.
听我说 我们听到的是Bennett叫 Franklin把那人弄出国去
Maybe Bennett changed his mind.
或许Bennett改变主意了
Either way, our priority is to keep Franklin in play.
不管怎样 我们的首要任务是让Franklin继续行动
So we just let him kill the bomber? If necessary, yes.
- 所以我们就让他杀了炸弹犯? - 如果有这必要 是的
That wasn't the deal.
方案不是这样的
The bomber's the only way to prove that Brody's innocent.
炸弹犯是唯一能够证明Brody清白的人
And stopping Franklin now would blow your cover
现在要阻止Franklin的话 会暴露你的身份
and Javadi's back in Tehran.
而Javadi已经回德黑兰了
You get that, right?
这点你知道的 对吧?
Until Franklin is clear, I want all teams to stand down.
在Franklin离开之前 我要所有小队都解除戒备
All teams, acknowledge standing down.
所有小队 告知戒备解除
Bravo here, standing down. Alpha Team standing down.
- 这里是B队 解除戒备 - Al队 解除戒备
Carrie, acknowledge.
Carrie 请告知
Carrie?
Carrie?
Carrie, what the fuck are you doing?
Carrie 你他妈干什么啊?
Carrie, go back to the van! Saul promised me this guy alive.
- Carrie 回到车里去! - Saul保证我说会活捉这个人
Saul's not calling the shots here.
这里做决定的不是Saul
He promised me, goddamn it. Get him on the phone!
他向我保证过 该死的 让他接电话!
There's no time. Turn around!
没时间了 回去!
Carrie, turn around now, or we will stop you.
Carrie 立刻回去 不然我们会阻止你
This is your last warning.
这是最后一次警告
Listen to the man, Carrie.
听话 Carrie
Bravo, I am authorizing force. Take the shot. I repeat.
B队 我允许你们使用武力 开枪 我重复
- Let me. - Take the shot.
- 开枪 - 我来
Carrie, this is Quinn.
Carrie 我是Quinn
Break away. I'm sorry. I can't.
- 撤退 - 抱歉 我做不到
You're fucking us, Carrie. Months of work. Your work.
你他妈会毁了我们的 Carrie 几个月的努力 你的努力
I don't care. Carrie, I will take the shot.
- 我不在乎 - Carrie 我会开枪的
Window's closing, for Christ's sake!
快没机会了 看在上帝的份上!
He's in. Franklin is inside. Pick her up, for God's sake!
他进去了 Franklin进去了 去接她 看在老天的份上!
Go! Go!
去! 去!
Move it!
赶紧走!
Jesus Christ.
老天啊
What was the delay? I stopped her, didn't I?
怎么迟了? 我阻止她了 记得吗?
Go with her. I'm watching Franklin.
和她一起去 我来盯着Franklin
Hospital's on the line. Tell 'em we got a gunshot wound to the upper left bicep,
- 接通医院了 - 告诉他们伤员左臂肱二头肌上部中枪
significant bleeding, might have clipped an artery.
大量失血 很可能是打中了动脉
Hold on. You're gonna be all right.
坚持住 你不会有事的
Goddamn it!
该死的!
Fuck! Fuck!
操! 操!
- Quinn... - Yeah?
- Quinn... - 嗯?
Is the bomber dead?
炸弹犯死了吗?
- Yeah. - Fuck!
- 是的 - 操!
Fuck!
操!
Something's going on.
出事了
- Yeah, you got shot. - Yeah, no shit!
- 是啊 你中枪了 - 是啊 还敢说!
You shot me!
你打了我!
No, I mean, something's going on. None of this... None of this makes sense.
不 我是说 出事了 这些都...这些都说不通
Just breathe, okay? Deep breaths. Come on.
呼吸 好吗? 深呼吸 拜托
Come here.
过来
Come closer.
近点
Where the fuck is Saul?
Saul他妈死哪儿去了?
You have a good flight? Yeah, fine.
- 旅途愉快吗? - 啊 还好
Got me here.
活着到了
All the money is there.
所有的钱都在这里了
Hey. This way. Wait here.
- 喂 这边 - 等在这里
In another month, it's even hotter.
再过一个月 还会更热的
You won't believe.
热到你不敢相信
Maybe I use the $10 million to put in an air conditioner.
或许我可以用那一千万买台空调
There.
那里
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入